# Agnieszka Matyja UX designer

#### Contact



Wheathampstead St. Albans, AL4 8PB



+44 (0)7514 487 378



agnieszkamatyja93@gmail.com

## Skill Highlights

- Excellent communication skills
- Organised
- Team-focused
- Ouick learner
- Creative designer

## **Technical Skills**

- UX Design courses and design practice (150+ hours)
- Usability testing
- User research
- UI Design tools (Adobe XD, Balsamiq, Sketch, Axure RP)
- Jira
- Basic HTML, CSS
- Excel

## Languages

English (Fluent), Polish (Native), French (Intermediate)

## Interests

Modern Art, Gym (Les Mills), Travelling, Skiing, Favourite author: Margaret Atwood.

#### About me

I have recently discovered a passion for User Experience Design and Research. I am currently perfecting my skills in this direction and focusing on conducting user research and iterative improvement to my designs, so that they are functional, clear and pleasing to the eye.

See my work at: www.agaux.co.uk

## Experience

## English Teacher Barnwell Middle School, Stevenage

Teaching at Barnwell enhanced my ability to construct clear ideas. Working closely in a team of English teachers allowed me to broaden my communication competency and refine my interpersonal skills. I was awarded Employee of the Month title.

#### EFL Teacher Target English International, Hatfield

2019

A rapidly-changing and vibrant environment of a summer school expanded my adaptability skills. I gained the experience of being flexible with last-minute adjustments and working under pressure.

#### EFL Teacher Zespół Szkolno-Przedszkolny no. 2, Kraków

2017 - 2019

# **Volunteer** Salesian Centre of Education and Animation, Częstochowa 2011 - 2012

As a volunteer I was responsible for obtaining sponsorship and participating in workshops on psychology.

#### Leader of the Year The Centre of European Languages, University of Wroclaw,

Częstochowa

2012 - 2015

I was chosen as student body president of my year group during my Bachelor Studies. My duties encompassed organizing group's documents and liaising between students and teachers to ensure mutual understanding.

## Education

Masters, Jagiellonian University, Kraków

2015 - 2017

Subject: English Philology

Grade: Bardzo Dobry (UK equivalent: Distinction)

Bachelors, The Centre of European Languages, University of Wrocław, Częstochowa

2012 - 2015

Subject: English Philology

Grade: Bardzo Dobry (UK equivalent: First Class)